

export const Questions = [ 
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following includes Chrome's V8 JavaScript Engine?",
        optionA: "jQuery",
        optionB: "Java",
        optionc: "npm",
        optionD: "Node.js",
       Answer: "optionD"

}, 
{
    prompt: "Which of the following is not a programming language? ",
    optionA: "TypeScript",
    optionB: "Python",
    optionc: "Anaconda",
    optionD: "JAVA",
    Answer: "optionC"

},
{
    prompt: "Which of the following is not a type of computer code related to Program Execution? ",
    optionA: "Source code",
    optionB: "Bytecode",
    optionc: "Machine Code",
    optionD: "Hex Code",
    Answer: "optionD"


},

{
    prompt: "Python is _____ programming language.",
    optionA: "high-level",
    optionB: "mid-level",
    optionc: "low-level",
    optionD: "none of the above",
    Answer: "optionA"


},

{
    prompt: "Where is the meta tag only found?",
    optionA: "Last page",
    optionB: "Home Page",
    optionc: "Second Page",
    optionD: "Third Page",
    Answer: "optionB"


},



{
    prompt: "What is an element that does not have a closing tag called?",
    optionA: "Tag",
    optionB: "Empty element",
    optionc: "Closed element",
    optionD: "Meta Tag",
    Answer: "optionB"


},

{
    prompt: "Main memory is also referred to as:",
    optionA: "ALU",
    optionB: "CU",
    optionc: "CPU",
    optionD: "IAS",
    Answer: "optionC"


},

{
    prompt: " What should values always be enclosed in? ",
    optionA: "Quotation marks",
    optionB: "Commas",
    optionc: "Parenthesis",
    optionD: "Brackets",
    Answer: "optionA"


},

{
    prompt: "How many tags are in a regular element? ",
    optionA: "2",
    optionB: "1",
    optionc: "4",
    optionD: "5",
    Answer: "optionA"


},

{
    prompt: "WhatsApp concurrent model is implemented using _____ programming language.",
    optionA: "Java",
    optionB: "Node.js",
    optionc: "Erlang",
    optionD: "C",
    Answer: "optionC"


},





]